this is the video you guys been waiting
for play byplay of this amazing big ass
long ass Vlog as you see in the freaking
uh time right there I don't know how
what it says like 40 50 minutes I don't
know maybe less I'm not even sure
because I didn't even edit it yet did I
say edited yeah I did say that big bang
concert in Las Vegas I knew it took me a
while to get this video out but you know
your boy a little bit busy but now it's
here let's go
re-experience this big bang
experience it ain't a concert it's an
experience that's for sure probably one
of the best experience I had in my life
let's go let's
begin yes
J it's going to happen man it's going to
happen I'm already
dead it's going to get
[Music]
crazy
hey oh this is the best
[Music]
part
and it
begins this
is this is
[Applause]
[Music]
big let the electric fors
[Applause]
ring
[Music]
[Applause]
oh oh my
God they opened up with bang bang bang
and it just bang bang all across my face
pause not like that more like a boxing
match then what you really thought you
dirty
mind
guys you
[Applause]
[Music]
ready
sry yelling into the TV and some people
that's some fan service right there I
guess yelling into the
camera next song was stupid liar and
they had these platforms which I think
they had in every like concert where you
know it just it moves across the crowd
and it kind of closes like a walkway so
I didn't expect that I didn't really
expect that so I saw it movie like oh my
God and it went on top of me I'm looking
up like oh my God I see tayang and I see
top I see G Dragon they stepping on me
it's it's a
[Applause]
blessing I was also scared that that
[__] looked like it was shaking it was
gonna fall on me so
I died at a big bang concert I mean [__]
it's going to be in the headlines K-pop
YouTuber dies at Big Bang
concert that's sad as
hell Tang hitting them notes because
something about the live concerts that
you don't get from the actual Studio
obviously is that um you know uh you get
the extra stuff that they do ad libs and
stuff and they say things that you don't
really normally say in a album know what
I mean
[Applause]
wo next up is Haru Haru and that was
it's like a throwback you know it's
everybody's one of everybody's favorites
like songs that big bang sings uh
obviously it's famous for that mvy
that's super sad and yeah I mean you
could just feel it in the crowd it just
feels nice when everybody just sings
together and then Big Bang is like
directing them in
[Applause]
[Music]
everything
[Applause]
[Music]
I can see you I can see
you then top being
[Music]
top
a next song is loser I didn't get really
good footage of that because they were
pretty far in the back even though I was
pretty close up close the stage is
pretty big so they were like in the
middle back but it was still pretty epic
and I mean tayang hit those notes I mean
you you already know those are like my
[Applause]
favorites
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm a
[Music]
loser
and like I said before they he adds a
little bit extra ad living and you know
play with the crowd of doing some extra
singing and you know I like that kind of
[Applause]
stuff feel
[Music]
it blue started playing one of my
favorite songs of Big Bang as
[Applause]
[Music]
well and blue has like this aura about
it something about like some big bang
songs that have like auras about it it's
like magical I don't know if it's like I
only feel that or and if y'all feel that
but I feel that and you know it's the
crowd singing just the atmosphere just
the lights and everything just put
together it's just an amazing concert I
don't
[Applause]
[Music]
know then they started talking I've been
here so many times and I am inspired by
this
[Music]
the show the lights the Productions and
all the other great artists that have
perform here and most of all Sury
started
preaching I feel sobody from West Coast
anybody from East
Coast any anybody from
[Music]
Asia so good so good where's my ladies
at
are you guys feeling good
[Applause]
tonight you guys are
amazing I'm so excited to come come I'm
so excited to come
to I know you guys are some of the
greatest greatest friends in
the how is the show so
far you good
you
like yeah super sexy
f tour in the
US make some noise for yourself Make
some noise for
yourself and then after they're done
talking they teased us with some bad boy
and they started singing Bad Boy which
bad boy is also one of my favorite songs
from their live album
y
ready I'm going to sing but I want you
to sing along with me can you do
that can you do
that
[Applause]
sexyx
[Music]
all my L
say see one more time
say all
[Music]
right
I
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
then they started saying if you
definitely one of uh the fans favorites
especially like it's very slow pace very
emotional kind of raw
feel then Sury came into the picture
give me some [__] nice B
and he performed strong baby uh crack
crack crack uh definitely one of my
favorite am I did I say it right strong
B it's strong baby right it's definitely
one of my favorites uh I'm glad he
actually performed I I was expecting you
know got a a talk to you or uh let's
talk about love but he performed strong
Bay one of his old school uh um like
first solo
[Music]
songs
[Applause]
woo
[Music]
[Applause]
w
[Music]
[Applause]
make some nice
[Music]
Ladies One More
[Applause]
[Music]
Time
next up is dayung
[Music]
[Applause]
solo I just love dayung's voice so
[Music]
good TP killed it with doom da like
literally killed it
[Music]
[Applause]
is going to hit
[Music]
[Applause]
literally that firework startled me but
I didn't move that camera though I I was
staying focused and then he killed it
after mass media holy [__] he just his
whole suit was like I it's that famous
painting I forgot I don't know if it's
by Picasso or is it by Picasso no I
don't know but he had that famous suit
he has a suit it was interesting and he
just killed it just killed it Doom da
all day Doom dollar all over your face
tayang Den saying eyes nose and lips
such a beautiful performance his voice
is amazing and even though he gave us a
little bit extra like I said in a live
concert they give you a little bit extra
remixes and ad libs and I love
it
[Music]
[Applause]
good
[Music]
everybody topping GD Zoda yo killed it
they were just so cool that whole song
is about being cool dope and chill and
look how badass they are to be
honest
[Music]
G baby give me give me give me no not
do can you give me give me give
[Music]
me then GD and Tang performed good boy
and GD and Tang went in especially D
Dragon my
[Music]
God go there we go huh here we go huh
you ready you ready you ready I'm ready
get
it let's go get it get go let's
[Applause]
[Music]
go basically G Dragon was humping that
camera though I'm just saying what the
hell
[Applause]
[Music]
G Dragon then performed the solo crooked
and he basically got
[Music]
[Applause]
wet
[Music]
[Applause]
D Dragon came out his traditional big
fluffy hat and they all performed U um
silver
[Music]
yeah 1 2 3
[Applause]
[Music]
next up is
baby
[Music]
[Applause]
at the end G Dron had to call out the
squad you know he his Squad
[Music]
[Applause]
call it ends and they have a final talk
you know T starting with tay young then
top saying a few words if you guys
having fun saying
yeah see yeah yeah see yeah yeah yeah
yeah now
three
[Applause]
wow swey boy you know I had a really
great time today what's up
up when we do come back will you guys be
there you
sure all right
okay there a promise
huh
promise almost over you I had so much
fun
today you guys com
truth thank you so much for spending
tonight together with
us I will never foret tonight I hope to
see your
game I really know you
[Applause]
guys
thank you for coming today I had such a
really good time tonight with you
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm so happy to Day song doing some
dance moves looking sexy acting sexy you
know what I'm saying doing some Michael
Jackson is like it was kind of like a
Michael Jackson it was a Michael Jackson
beat
[Applause]
definitely hey hey hey hey
yeah
God oh
[Applause]
my all right guys all right who's going
the first B heyy right here right here
hey right
here right here let me show let me
shut all right
figas figas I said fig what's up figas
it's
[Applause]
de take it up take it up hey hey go
ahead take it up I don't have nothing
man take it
up take all all
over take it take it take
it the meat
[Applause]
[Music]
now
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah h
h
[Applause]
yeah that's up it's so who's going to
take this hot blown
guy all right
[Applause]
guys Vegas I had so so so much fun today
hey go stop because Vegas is my this is
biggest we are in biggas right
now G Dragon turn to talk I hope you
guys going to win
[Applause]
tonight just kill it hold the F ass
Hotel I want to say really thank you so
much coming today stop it thank you so
much all right my leader Che go
ahead
[Applause]
so we only have one Soul
left I just want to say thank you for
coming today and always showing us so
much love and coming to our M tour thank
you very
much so prob real is album m a d and e
right we still have our FL made coming
very soon so make sure you check it out
don't miss out okay then Su interrupted
and started preaching
[Applause]
again you guys have some confus this is
not mean just like give me a CH it's
like a it's a heart it's like it's like
a little heart yeah some us friends tell
me man what is that is it give the CH
something no this is
hot not hot yeah we are hot it's heart
hearts you know Hearts you
know heart so cute
right it's so H right now just use it
just take a picture and post your instam
something all right
so sign to
signify it's going the last
s you
[Applause]
ready y'all still with me
love so
tonight fantastic [__]
[Applause]
[Music]
baby like when G Dragon said
[__]
fantastic baby he literally said that
just say yes once again [__]
fantastic
[Music]
[Applause]
baby
[Music]
everybody w
thank you so much you guys are amazing
thank you
so there were supposed to end but then
they came out and played we like to
party love that song even though it does
sound like B
[Music]
Hills
we
[Music]
[Applause]
get
[Music]
Lou thank you so much you know who we
[Applause]
[Music]
are
[Applause]
[Music]
good I love
[Applause]
[Music]
you love you love
[Applause]
you
but it ended on a good
note and they even added like more extra
stuff you know like playing around with
babay and just like adding a little bit
extra like some fan service you know
what I'm saying something that you know
get your money's worth and that's what I
got I literally got my money's worth
hell
[Applause]
yeah see what you me yeah oy oy
[Music]
[Applause]
oh say
oh
[Applause]
thank
Youk thank Youk
[Music]
you
yeah that bad that
[Music]
[Applause]
bad because ends and then we saw a lot
of you awesome beautiful sexy beautiful
people who recognized me and who are
standing next to me but you know we have
to concentrate on big bang big bang
first and if you want to you know
interact with me or talk with me or take
a picture with me then let's do it so we
basically saw a bunch of y'all and
here's a clip of some of
y'all oh yeah and
then as you already
know this happened let's go
yeah yeah thanks man I think I say
you're the re he saw me reaction guy you
know me he's on YouTube what yo high
five
man all right y'all I just want to do a
play byplay kind of thing on this big
big Vlog this is a long ass Vlog I'm
sorry if it's too long hope you guys
enjoyed it I did this kind of thing so
you can have at least some sort of
experience with me and big bang and I
just had a blast it was totally my
money's worth uh big bang is the best
concert I've been to it it's the
ultimate concert and everything and more
happened Big Bang You Are Forever gonna
be my
favorites hands down I had fun hoped you
guys had fun watching the little clips
and you know me explaining things here
and there and hopefully you give this
video a like share it comment down below
what was your favorite part and yeah
share this with everyone subscribe to
the channel this is your boy JRE and
thank you for watching love you all my
sex beautiful people listen to K-pop it
feels good listen to music in general it
feels good and keep on dream dreaming
dreamers dream believe do repeat you
keep on dreaming you put hard work into
it it might come true all right y'all
bye weding confetti and choc straight to
the chorus in
one Del dangerous can't resist you in
different sizes many flavors you're so
much better sweet and moisted do you
want to so delicious
D feel nervous so weak around you I
stutter and I can't say hi baby girl
you're just my time you're making me
feel nervous I can't resist it I can't
get you off my mind baby
girl hey girl choose your bias what's a
bias what's a bias yeah what's a bias do
you have a favorite group yeah do you
like someone from that group I'm I'm not
I'm not sure you're not sure stop
stuttering they gave us bags for our
backs I don't know what's going on looks
like I'm a drug drug Smuggler what what
you doing hi no over this roaring it we
about to go into sound check that's
right